Welcome to the family
Escobar: Paradise Lost is a thriller, romance
film directed by Andrea Di Stefano.
For Pablo Escobar family is everything.
When young surfer Nick falls for Escobar's niece, Maria, he finds his life on the
line when he's pulled into the dangerous world of the family business.
Pablo Escobar, played by Benicio del Toro.
Nick, played by Josh Hutcherson.
Dylan, played by Brady Corbet.
Maria, played by Claudia Traisac.
Drago, played by Carlos Bardem.
Anne, played by Ana Girardot.
Escobar: Paradise Lost (also known as Paradise Lost) is a 2014 romantic thriller film
written and directed by Andrea Di Stefano in his directorial debut.
The film chronicles the life of a surfer who falls in love while working with his brother in
Colombia and finds out that the girl's uncle is Colombian drug lord Pablo Escobar.
RADiUS-TWC acquired the North American distribution
rights of the film in February 2014.
The film premiered at the 2014 Toronto International Film Festival on September 11,
2014 and had a limited release  in the United States on June 26, 2015.
The film explores themes of surfer, murder, murderer.
The tone is emotional and intense.